so here with her thoughts on women's
history month is nightly show
contributor Robin
the welcome to the show Robert thanks
Larry now for women's History Month I
just wanted to shed light on a
phenomenon that can help people
understand women better oh that's great
well uh what is it black lady sign
language there it is wow okay this is
kind of cool so what is black ladies
sign language then well you might have
noticed that black ladies use a lot of
hand gestures you know non-verbal
communication chances are there's a
black lady in your office and she's
probably named
Rhonda and you might misunderstand her
sometimes right like you might think
Rhonda's being hostile when she's not or
you might think she's not being hostile
when she
is oh wow I I can see how that would be
problematic right yes so think of this
as my public service announcement so you
can understand Rhonda a little bit
better that's great okay so how does it
work okay all right let me give you a
few examples right number one the single
hand clap all right now this can be used
to express happiness or anger and
learning to tell the difference can
actually save your life all right watch
great great okay oh that's my
song right okay very different from
would you say to
me okay I know at first glance they can
look the same but weren't those the same
no no no no no not at all Larry no here
just watch in slow motion all right my
song okay versus
what see the finger roll is the subtle
difference oh my God I would never know
to look for that thing it's the finger
thing that's right now you will
fascinating black lady sign language
thank you all right well let's move on
to our next question okay this is the
double hand clap versus the double hand
clap on syllables
all right okay now this one's easier to
spot but it can be deceptive okay so
check this out all right yay great job
on your performance oh yeah that's yeah
see that that that just looks like
regular Applause well that's correct
because it is okay but compare that to
the double hand clap on syllables
syllables again what did you say to me
Larry I didn't I didn't say anything I
was don't interrupt me l r
I'm just Kidd I'm just kid I'm just but
now but now you can see how effective it
is right man I was I was yeah yeah the
double hand clap on syllables is used to
emphasize a point wow that was so
effective Rob that's um it it really
emphasizes in angry point right oh yeah
well not necessarily It's tricky because
it can be used for anger or excitement
such as oh my God these shoes are on
sale nice that's crazy man that's crazy
okay now we're only we're allowed to do
that oh oh I'm okay it's cool but uh
don't let it happen
again got
it got it all right so time for our
final black lady sign language gesture
now this this is a big one the double
handwave versus the double hand wve pull
b o wow that sounds complicated it it is
complicated but but you've been doing
well so far so all right let's start
with the double hand okay so see I'm
just waving both hands just double hand
wave hi it's cute right oh yeah I like
yeah hey right right right right great
yeah that's nice but if I do the double
hand wve pullback okay who said what to
me see see this is a woman who's at her
Wits End she's not in a space to reason
you should probably leave the room wow I
think I saw that on World Star once
thing absolutely very good it was a
scary moment it yes no it can be quite a
thing all right well so let's wrap this
up by showing you all three in action
right this is uh what I like to call the
black lady sign language combo
platter all right to better understand
the wonderful black ladies in your life
you have to pay attention and say
goodbye to all your preconceived notions
and if you ever get confused just
re-watch this segment do you hear me
Larry yes yes okay I hear you Robin D
everybody